["All About Me" playing]
♪ Boys make empty promises
That they can never fill... ♪
[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
New connections were made.
and an ex's arrival left one boy shocked.
Oh. my... That's... Bro. that's my ex.
Oh. shit.
♪ It's all about me ♪
Hello!
-[Imani] Oh. shit.
-That's his ex?
That's my ex.
Hey. Marco.
♪ It's all about me ♪
Bro.
[laughs]
♪ I'm out here paying my dues ♪
[song ends]
[narrator] Tonight...
...temperatures rise again.
[theme song playing]
["Right Words" playing]
♪ What if
I could go further back in time? ♪
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
Marco is not happy.
He's sat with his ex. Hannah.
who just showed up again out of the blue.
and they served pancakes.
which always repeat on him.
Much like Hannah.
I just wanna know. like.
if you really are kind of. like. open.
Man.
I thought we had a good time together.
but there were some things with you
that were missing in my life
and. you know. what I look for in a woman.
If you would've. uh. talked to me more
and opened up a little bit.
you would've known more things about me.
I feel like you don't know
anything about me.
But this is the most
we've ever talked. I feel.
Like. without you staring at your phone.
I know we didn't
leave things off. like. the best way...
Hell. no. I think we could've been
more mature and kinda talked about it.
Yeah. but then again.
you weren't open to talking much.
I was like.
"Yeah. don't... don't come back."
[laughing] "Don't come back." Wow.
[Marco] I was just. like. you know...
Wow. okay.
Obviously. I was true.
I was honest with you the whole time.
Yeah. you were. Only thing that changed.
you're a lot more open with your feelings.
So. I was like.
"Okay. that's a new Marco."
You were never open about your feelings.
You're really putting me on blast here
about how I don't open up.
-Uh. Sorry.
-Fuck.
She's fucking gorgeous.
You think he's gonna fold?
I think it's just fucked up.
Are you. like. 100% for Hannah?
I think I just need to hear it. like...
Yeah. I'm not... I'm not open.
-I'm not open.
-You're not open. 100%? Okay.
I wish the best for you.
And I got your back. I always do.
Yeah.
You know. it's something...
You coming in here and exploring
other options with other men
is not gonna be easy for me to watch.
Obviously. you came here for me.
but there's a lot of nice guys here.
you know what I mean?
-So... Cheers to that.
-Cheers.
-Best of luck here.
-Yeah.
If my girl came back on
that I dated for a long-ass time.
I'd be interested
to open that door back open.
It sucks to say that...
-But it's the truth.
-It's the truth.
It's happening. It's happening!
-She's coming for a chat.
-Make her a space.
-Hello. ladies!
-[all] Hi!
All right. guys. take in Hannah.
These are great girls. Bye. guys.
[all] Bye!
Hi. ladies.
-[Anna] You are so gorgeous.
-Oh. my God. thank you.
[Hannah O] You guys
are all so pretty. Oh. my God.
-[all laughing]
-[Hannah O] Wow!
Get to the orange couch. gentlemen.
-How are you feeling?
-Good. bro. Good.
[Mike] Hot seat. baby.
Get in there real close. boys.
My dawg. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm... you know...
I said. "I know you came here for me.
but I know where my heart's at."
She's a girl who
I really felt comfort with in the time.
but I could never really open up to her.
It wasn't 'cause I wasn't feeling it.
It wasn't because she did something to me.
It's because I was scared.
But Hannah brought something out of me
that this Hannah didn't.
Obviously. he is with Hannah. which
is funny. Her name is Hannah as well.
[all] Yeah. literally.
But obviously. I came in
trying to explore that connection
because we kind of left things
so up in the air.
But to see if there was something more.
or maybe just the closure I needed.
-Mm-hmm.
-And he is pretty closed off.
How does that make you feel?
I mean. that whole conversation was just...
I don't know. it was a bit...
-Threw me off a little bit.
-[Imani] Yeah.
He made it clear. okay. he's closed off.
But then there was times he'd be like...
-You felt like the door was cracked?
-Kind of open.
He's like. "I don't know how I'm gonna
feel watching you talking to other guys."
-[all] Oh!
-[Hannah O] Yeah!
[Imani] When a guy says that...
But the thing is. I don't know if he's
saying that to not hurt my feelings or...
-[all] No. No.
-I don't care. he should be straight up.
That gives me cracked-door energy.
-Yeah.
-The door is still cracked.
I do. I believe that too.
You guys. if you wanna get to know her.
go get to know her.
Obviously. it's gonna be very hard for me.
I'd really respect. you know.
"Hey. I'm really feeling Hannah."
I'd be like. "Great. bro. go for it."
But just let me know first.
[Marco] In this moment. I'm feeling
at ease with how I left with Hannah O.
As a man and a man of my word. I stick
to my feelings. I stick to my heart.
You know. my heart's with Hannah.
and not Hannah O.
So. I wanted to make the decision as clear
as I could in the most respectful manner.
-Good chat. bro.
-Yes. sir.
Do your thing. you know?
All you gotta do is rock out.
and we're gonna respect it.
[narrator] Rob's asking Hannah
about his chances with Carmen.
'Cause he's a snake handler.
Rob's got a snake tattooed on his arm.
And because I'm a comedian.
I've got the words "childhood trauma"
tattooed on mine.
Okay. Hannah. I'm gonna cut to the chase.
So. you and Carmen
are really good friends.
[Hannah W] You want the scoop?
I mean. I don't know about the scoop.
I just wanna let you know
that I'm very intentional about her.
Yeah. I heard.
-Is that the word on the street?
-Yeah.
Yeah. I'm serious about her.
and I just thought I'd let you know
and maybe ask if you had any advice.
I know she has a strong connection.
I know going for her is probably crazy.
but I don't really care. I like her.
Aw. I like that a lot.
Okay. so here's the thing with Carmen.
So. her and Kenzo.
both from Scottsdale. you know?
They got that going on.
Home court advantage.
-Do you know what I mean?
-Yeah.
But her situation is still very new.
Right.
So. it's almost like it'd be a disservice
for her not to get to know you.
And she likes that you're funny.
Yeah. I love making her laugh.
When she smiles.
it gives me a little hit of serotonin.
But I do think
I wanna be a little more serious.
-Right. Have that mix.
-Because I feel like I just...
I've kind of just tried to be goofy.
-make her laugh. break the ice.
-Which is good.
But I think I'm trying
to turn up the heat a little bit.
-Definitely.
-The things that matter.
Turn up the heat.
I think you know what to do.
-She's definitely interested.
-That's good.
So that's... Shoot. that's huge.
[Rob] Carmen. she's so hard to read.
I feel like
she's definitely keeping her distance.
I want to definitely flirt with her.
definitely try to get
her head turned my way.
And I'd really like to kiss her.
-You wanna go for a chat?
-[Carmen] Yeah.
Where should we go?
Maybe get in the shade.
[Carmen] Yeah. shade.
It's extra. extra hot today.
[chuckles] Yeah. It's nice.
What's up?
[sighs] How was your sleep?
-It was good.
-It was good?
It was honestly kinda nice
to sleep out here though.
I believe that.
It's the perfect temperature at night.
What is your aspiration in life?
Aspiration?
Honestly. I don't think that far out
in advance. if I'm being honest.
Hypothetically. in a crazy. wild scenario.
would you be down to. like...
If I was like. "Hey. next month
I'm probably gonna go to Brazil
and hang out for a little bit.
catch some snakes. see the sights."
Are you going? You coming with me?
I would come with. but I wouldn't
come with to catch the snakes.
Well. yeah. No.
you don't have to do that. But...
I just get to come hang out in Brazil?
-Yeah.
-That. I could do.
But you'd. like...
I would say... [clicks tongue]
What is the proximity
I'm gonna have to snakes?
Let's say twice a week you gotta go on
a little adventure with me. You have to.
Then we can do whatever you want.
Did you not see how I reacted to the toad?
The toad. yeah.
I know. but was it not exciting?
Was it not exhilarating?
I would just love to get you in a creek
somewhere and show you all the things.
You did not just say
you'd love to get me in a creek.
Carmen. I would love...
Never had a boy say that to me in my life.
I'd love to get you in a creek somewhere
and just show you
all the things that are there...
that are right there. and no one
ever sees them. And it's beautiful.
I don't go in creeks
'cause I know there's shit in there.
Yeah. Well. we gotta get you in one.
I think you would love it. I really do.
My whole heart thinks
you would really like it.
So what were you chitchatting
with Hannah about?
-You.
-I knew.
But why are you trying
to get the intel from my girls?
-I'm not.
-What did she say?
The talk mainly was about...
I was letting her know
that I'm very intentional
about getting to know you.
and I like you.
and I have feelings. [sniggers]
-Feelings?
-And I have feelings.
What'd she say?
She said. "Okay."
No. me and Kay Kay were trying to...
We were literally putting words
into what Hannah was saying over here.
Nah. I mean.
she just said that I have a chance.
And that. uh.
that she's glad
that I'm serious about you.
That's mainly what I wanted to say.
'cause I know y'all are close.
Yeah.
I was like. "If she doesn't like me.
I'm gonna have problems."
So I was like. "I'm gonna let her know
I'm all about Carmen."
I can appreciate that.
Good. you should.
You should appreciate it.
I just said I appreciate it.
Yes. And I said. "Good."
So what. is Soul Ties the serious area?
[Destiny. Matia] Soul Ties.
It's hidden away. Nobody can see you.
They hear you. though.
[Destiny] They hear you. though!
-It's like...
-[phone chimes]
-[all] Whoa!
-I got a text!
[cheering]
-[phone chimes]
-I got a text!
[cheering]
[Imani] What it say. girl?
"Islanders. today The Villa and Casa Amor
will be competing
in a game of Raunchy Races."
[all whoop]
"The winning villa will party. #PuckerUp."
#It'sOn.
[cheering]
[Kassy] We better beat them.
We're not no losers.
We won last night. we're winning today.
-We gotta be the raunchiest...
-I'm the raunchiest.
-...and the quickest. Let's go.
-[kisses]
I don't know what it is
with me and competitions.
Like. this little monster
comes out of me. [laughs]
-We don't lose.
-[Imani] Let's go!
Casa Amor does not lose.
Last night. took an L.
but tonight we bounce back.
We gonna win this one!
We got demolished on this last challenge.
This is OG. This is the lion's den.
We're coming in hot. We're ready to go.
We're about to make this score even-even.
1-1. baby. Come on.
[narrator] Coming up...
Get up in there!
It's time to get it on.
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
It's time for Raunchy Races.
a head-to-head challenge
requiring speed. skill.
and a total lack of shame.
We gotta be the quickest
-and the raunchiest.
-Yes.
They're gonna be coming for us.
you guys. because we won already.
We don't fucking lose. all right?
I don't give a fuck about good luck.
We don't need fucking luck. We gotta win.
[narrator] Casa Amor and the main villa
will simultaneously receive
identical texts.
The first team to complete the task
wins the race.
And the overall winner gets themselves
not just a party. but a "part-ay."
"Share a smooch with the islander
you're sharing a bed with. Go!"
-Come here!
-[Kenzo] Go. go. go!
[all cheer]
It's not like you were in a romantic date
with someone and you shared a besito.
And. like... [moans]
...no. it's time to get it on.
"Share a smooch with the Islander
you're sharing a bed with."
[Hannah W] Get it! Get on top of him!
You better ride him! Ride him!
[Destiny] I'm definitely.
you know. coming with the theatrics.
That's one thing I do.
-[phone chimes]
-Guys.
Fuck. The villa won the point!
[all screaming]
"The villa won the point"?
-Are you fucking me?
-What the hell?
Maybe our energy is low. What is it?
We can do a little bit
more passionate. a little bit more sexy.
Yeah. Maybe.
Let's go crazy.
I definitely didn't feel no sparks flying.
I felt like it could've been more.
If it would've been more.
we would've got a point.
-Come on. lock in!
-[phone chimes]
"A girl with the least amount of tattoos
must sit on the lap of a boy
who is a Virgo and give him a kiss. Go."
[all] Who's a Virgo?
Least tattoos! Least tattoos!
-Go ahead. go ahead!
-Just go! Just go! Get on him.
-Give me a kiss.
-Okay.
[all whooping]
[Kenzo] Keep going! Keep going!
[whooping continues]
The kiss with Ashley was a little juicy.
Like. it's absolutely crazy
how much experience I've gotten
through this whole experience.
[Leonardo] Iceberg!
[Keenan] Iceberg. Good work!
[Bergie] That's a good start.
-[phone chimes]
-"A girl with the least amount of tattoos
must sit on the lap of a boy
who is a Virgo and give him a kiss. Go."
Here's a Virgo.
[Hannah W] Where's the Virgo?
-Give him a what?
-[all] A kiss! Kiss him!
[all cheer]
[Kay Kay] Get in there!
Yeah! Kiss him! Get in there!
[phone chimes]
"The villa has won the point"!
[all cheering]
Let's go! Let's fucking go!
[phones chimes]
"The villa has won the point."
[Kay Kay] You've got to be fucking me.
[phone chimes]
"A boy with the most tattoos
and a girl whose star sign is a goat
must share a slow and sexy kiss. Go."
Uh. me. Capricorn!
[Destiny] Let's go. baby!
Yeah! Make it nasty! Make it nasty!
Yeah! Let's go!
Slow and sexy!
Yeah. there it is. There it is.
There you go. Yeah. Get into it.
The kiss was good. It was hot.
And he's hot. so can't complain.
Who's the most tatted boy? Marco.
Oh. okay. Sorry.
Fuck.
Most tattoos and Capricorn.
Wanna be out here?
Sexy kiss! Sexy kiss! Sexy kiss!
[all cheering]
-[phone chimes]
-Oh. oh. oh!
The villa has won the fucking point!
-[phone chimes]
-"The villa has won the point."
Are you being for real?
-[Brandon] Damn.
-[Rob] Listen. it's okay.
[Hannah W] I definitely took it personal.
I'm like. "Dang.
what the hell was he doing?"
To show her. like.
that it was. you know. a good kiss.
[groans] Fuck. This is annoying.
-I don't like Marco kissing.
-I know. but it's just part of the game.
He's probably... We'll see how he reacted.
Knowing your partner's kissing other girls
and stuff is obviously not fun.
-[phone chimes]
-I got it. Hold on.
"Blondes have more fun. Kiss the girl
with the lightest hair color."
-Who's got blonde?
-Me.
-Come here.
-That's me.
[all cheering]
"Kiss a girl
with the lightest hair color. Go."
-Carmen.
-[Kay Kay] Do it!
-[Hannah W] Go in.
-[Kay Kay] Yeah!
It just felt so natural.
It felt good. I liked it a lot.
[Destiny] Good job. Rob. Good job. Car.
"Casa Amor has won the point"!
[all cheering]
Casa Amor.
Fuck!
So. that's gotta be Carmen.
Obviously. I'm a little bit jealous.
I really care about Carmen.
I miss her a lot. And it obviously sucks
that she probably had to kiss
some other boys over there.
but she hopefully saved
the real ones for me.
"The Islander who's been
coupled up the longest
must smooch the Islander of the
opposite sex they think is the hottest."
Yes! Yes!
There is no way my kiss with Brandon...
when I leaped into his lap...
there's no way Keenan was kissing somebody
more passionate than that.
"...they think is the hottest. Go."
Get your ass over here. Come on.
[all cheering]
[Keenan] Shit. I went for it. you know?
She's a gorgeous girl.
There's an interest there.
and I feel like that's important
to see if there's
that real physical chemistry.
And we for sure had it.
It was nice. fo' shit sho.
Get the fuck at it! Let's go!
Let's all fucking go!
Oh. shit.
We won this. We had to have.
[phone chimes]
"The villa has won the point"!
"The vill"... What?
"The villa has won the point."
Ain't no fucking way. Ain't no way.
[Destiny] Nah!
-I want a redo.
-There's no way.
Same. Something ain't right.
Are you feeling somebody over there? Hmm.
'Cause that was... He got to choose
who he got to kiss on that one.
And he won?
And he chose
to kiss that girl specifically? Hmm.
It do have me thinking. like.
"What's going on over there?"
[phone chimes]
"Get into your favorite sex position
with the Islander you fancy most."
[Leonardo] Ooh. damn!
[Johnnie] I haven't had
the touch from a man in months.
It gave me butterflies. which are like
butterflies for your vagina.
-Damn. mami.
-[laughs]
That was good.
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
You like to ride it?
[all laughing]
Oh. Junior!
Ay. the real question is.
what you gonna do with that information?
Pause. We need
to win this fucking challenge first.
We'll see after this party
how I'm feeling.
"Get into your favorite sex position
with the Islander you fancy the most. Go."
-Oh. shit. uh...
-Which one?
Go!
Pow. pow. pow. pow!
[all chanting] Pow. pow. pow!
And Matia was doing his little baby pumps.
I don't know. It was insane.
[Destiny] Give me some hips.
Yes. Kass. There we go.
[phone chimes]
"The villa has won the point."
-The villa won the point.
-[Hannah W] What the fuck?
It's 'cause you didn't
put your back into it.
Me? What was I supposed to...
You gotta really sell that shit.
I want to win this game so frickin' bad.
[phone chimes]
"The youngest girl twerks on a guy."
Oh. Imani twerking in a split.
The cheeks was clapping.
"Casa Amor has won the point."
I feel like these Casa Amor boys
are more competitive
than the boys we have at the villa.
-[phone chimes]
-"The youngest boy
must sensually kiss the neck of the girl
he most wants to share a bed with."
-[Imani] Get it.
-[Hannah W] Go for it!
Make it sensual!
There you go. Kay Kay.
The kiss with Kay Kay.
that was pretty electric.
[Destiny] There we go! Yeah. Brandon!
Kay Kay! Do that shit. Kay Kay!
Yeah!
Come on. Brandon. Whoo-hoo!
Te-he-he.
Whew.
[all] Go. go. go!
[Jonah] Kiss the neck!
[all cheering]
Get up in there!
I'm not gonna lie. I'm very confused.
The connection with Johnnie
is beyond undeniable.
It's just a really tough position
to be in.
End of the day. I have no idea
what Kassy is doing right now.
Who is the youngest boy
at the vill... Oh. it's Leo.
It's Leo.
[Destiny] You know
Leo took that advantage real bad.
"It was a game. babe."
I'm fine. [chuckles]
-[phone chimes]
-"Casa Amor has won the point"!
Whew. I love that.
-[phone chimes]
-"Casa Amor has won the point."
-[all] No way.
-What?
Damn. that's tragic.
I was pretty damn passionate
about that kiss.
Like. I fully was devouring
both sides of her neck.
[phone chimes]
"Choose an Islander
to have an underwater kiss with." Fuck.
-[Johnnie] Right here.
-[all] Go!
[Jonah] Mic. mic. mic. mic!
Get underwater. It's only five feet.
[Marco] Oh. that's fire.
-[Johnnie] Underwater.
-[Keenan] Go. go. go.
-They did it. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
-They did.
"Choose an Islander
to have an underwater kiss with."
Get it. Carmen. Go!
-Who you choosing?
-Take your fucking mics off.
[Hannah W] Go. Brandon! There we go.
[all] Underwater!
[Hannah W] There we go!
Yeah!
I've never kissed anyone
underwater before.
and I probably won't do it again
because I opened my mouth
mid-kiss and nearly drowned.
"Casa Amor has won the point."
[Branson] Carmen and I.
we were the dive team.
It was bang. bang. and jump.
[phone chimes]
"A girl whose name is the same
spelled in reverse
has to smooch
with the boy with the most tattoos. Go."
[Imani] The same reversed?
The same in reverse. Hannah.
[Imani] Go. Hannah!
Oh. yeah!
Yes!
-Keep going!
-[Imani] That was good.
Do they have. like. an "Anna" over there?
Watch there be another Hannah. [scoffs]
-Most tattoos.
-Marco.
[all whooping]
[Marco] She was over to me
on top of me before I even knew it.
Can't say I hated it.
That's gonna be Hannah on the other side.
Yeah. it's Hannah. Me and Hannah.
I didn't know Hannah
spelled backwards was Hannah.
-[phone chimes]
-"Casa Amor has won the point"!
Let's go!
I'm happy I won that one
because it was me against him.
[narrator] It's time for the results.
But who's the big winner?
I mean. the real winner
is television. obviously.
But which of this lot came out on top?
-We can do this.
-[phone chimes]
"The final scores are in."
Shit.
"It's a tie."
"And therefore.
both villas have won a party tonight"!
[Jonah] Pool!
♪ Summer Young ♪
♪ The future's made for us together... ♪
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Raunchy Races was such a hit.
Hasbro bought the rights.
And this Christmas.
they're bringing it out as a board game.
Imagine the fun you'll have
playing Raunchy Races with your granny.
How do you think the boys are reacting?
[all cheering]
-That was a blast.
-Hey. boys. That was lit. That was lit.
Ain't no way Keenan
was kissing somebody harder than that.
Nah. nah. definitely not.
But if anything. I think he turned over
and kissed whoever was next to him.
Maybe it was quicker. There were
a couple texts that were clearly you.
-Clearly Kay Kay. Coupled up the longest...
-And we won them.
So you know he's over there...
[Kay Kay] "What's she doing?" [laughs]
And he's doing
the Keenan in the challenge.
-[all laughing]
-"Fuck. man."
-He take that shit so serious.
-I know.
I'm not ecstatic that she's
doing whatever. but it's a challenge.
She's supposed to have fun. And hopefully.
these challenges will help her
get out of her comfort zone a little bit
and maybe explore different connections.
Not that I want her to do that.
but if I'm the only one that's testing
our connection. is it truly being tested?
I feel like it's the first time
y'all really got to see Keenan.
if I'm being so serious.
Just having that freedom again.
it opens up some of the things
that I wasn't happy about.
but I owe it to myself just to be here.
be in this fucking moment.
And I don't give a damn. I will live
in this fucking moment. period.
Kissing the shorty's neck. I realized
I didn't "kiss her" kiss her. right?
But I was kissing up on her neck.
And then when
she was riding my shit. bruv.
I was leaning back like.
"Oh. God." I was like. "Wait."
Bruh. I know my girl's out there
probably doing the same shit.
But it didn't really bother me at all.
'Cause end of the day. it's a challenge.
Did anybody feel like they had fireworks
during their kiss during this challenge?
Look at her smiling.
A little bit.
I seen a little passion.
I saw some thrustin'.
We both just gravitate
towards each other a lot.
[Hannah W] Yeah.
[Kassy] Even just sitting down.
we're always next to each other.
-Yeah.
-So just. like. kissing was...
surprising. It was good.
Better than I thought. so...
Have you kissed him before?
-Yeah.
-[Hannah W] Okay.
How many kisses is this?
He did kiss me yester...
Oh. I didn't tell y'all!
-Oh. damn. I didn't know that.
-[Carmen] What?
Yesterday. um. he kissed me.
and he just wanted to express
that it was only me he was interested in.
-Dang.
-[Kassy] Yeah.
-He put it on the floor.
-Yeah.
Do you think that if you were to leave
Matia behind and go back to the villa.
would you be thinking about him?
Yeah. I probably would question
and be like. "What if?"
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
-But I still don't know.
[Kassy] My head's all over the place.
Maybe that's why
I got a headache from the game.
'cause I'm thinking too much.
I can't help but admit
that me and Matia have something.
Absolutely enjoyed that challenge.
I feel like I'm getting
more out of my shell every day.
and I'm just enjoying
this journey of growth that I'm on.
Before coming into the villa.
I'd kissed five girls.
It's absolutely crazy
how much experience I've gotten.
No complaints. [chuckles]
I even lost my voice a little bit.
-I'm excited. Tonight's gonna be lit.
-Hell. yeah.
[Marco] I'm ready
to turn up and party big!
[all cheering]
Let's go!
-Let's go!
-Let's fucking go!
[narrator] The challenge was a tie.
so they've all won a party.
Essentially. it's like
every other night in the villa.
but with adhesive rhinestones.
Yay! Adhesive rhinestone party.
♪ I'm a freak. move or reach ♪
♪ You should keep me on a leash... ♪
We're all wearing white.
About to throw on the all-black.
Craziest ball tickle ever?
Not knowing what the hell
is really happening on the other side.
♪ I'm a freak. move or reach ♪
♪ You should keep me on a leash ♪
♪ I'm the hottest on the scene ♪
♪ My little Miss Gasolina ♪
♪ Freak. move or chic ♪
♪ You should keep me on a leash ♪
I'm really excited. y'all. [giggles]
Our first little...
Well. my first get-down with y'all.
I wonder what Mike's up to.
I wonder what Jonah's up to.
I wonder what Leo's up to.
I wonder what Keenan's up to.
We're just trying to focus
on being baddies right now.
Get pumped up. get pumped up.
Get pumped up! Get pumped up!
[singsongy] We are gonna have so much fun.
Come in.
You gonna style us up
with the rhinestones?
[yelps]
Yeah. it's good.
♪ Move or reach
You should keep me on a leash ♪
♪ I'm the hottest on the scene ♪
♪ My little Miss Gasolina ♪
♪ Freak. move or chic ♪
♪ You should keep me on a leash ♪
♪ I'm the hottest on the scene ♪
♪ My little Miss Gasolina ♪
♪ I'm a freak ♪
♪ Freak ♪
[song ends]
[all cheering]
♪ I don't think we're crazy ♪
Cheers!
♪ Now you're always on my mind ♪
♪ Yeah. you know it's you I'm chasing ♪
♪ And I can't leave you behind ♪
♪ This is love ♪
♪ I know that this is love ♪
♪ Ooh. yeah ♪
♪ This is love ♪
♪ I know that this is love ♪
[song ends]
[chattering]
[narrator] Johnnie's got
a burning question for Leonardo.
Let me guess. Is it. "Why didn't
we get any adhesive rhinestones?"
I did wanna talk to you.
like. at some point.
I kind of wanna know where your head's at.
Because I haven't
really felt this way in a while
where I'm connected to somebody.
And I wanted to know
that you were on the same wavelength.
You are in a couple.
and you have something that right now
is not here. and I get to have fun.
-Can I reassure you of something?
-What?
You're a second option to nobody.
You're the one.
You are the It girl.
In all my time being here.
I've never connected to someone this fast.
All bullshit aside. I would go hard
for you in the real world. Um...
Okay.
Yeah. would you be okay with a kiss?
Yeah. Stand up.
-Oh!
-Yeah.
♪ Just let me fade away ♪
♪ Into the night ♪
It felt like there was
literally no one else in the house
except for the two of us.
♪ We'll be all right ♪
Definitely the feelings for Johnnie
have increased from that kiss.
So. yeah.
Now it could be some trouble.
♪ You gotta let us die ♪
[song ends]
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Over in Casa.
Carmen's grabbing snake charmer Rob.
I once saw Rob charm a Burmese python.
He took it for dinner.
complimented its eyes.
and whisked it off
for its favorite Broadway show.
The old snake charmer.
I just wanna get deeper with you.
Okay.
Are you down for that?
Yeah.
What are you looking to get out of this?
I would like to start a relationship.
but I'm also very much a realist.
I'm just open to whatever happens.
you know what I mean?
Like. I've got to the point in my life
where I'm so content
and happy with my life alone
-that I would just like an addition.
-It's hard for you.
There's really great girls here.
and they're beautiful.
but I like you. and
I wanna get to know you.
And I wanna give us a shot.
While I have a good relationship
at the villa that I wanna respect.
and that's still important to me.
I'm still open to getting to know you.
Compared to Destiny or Imani.
who are a hundred percent into Casa.
there's probably like 50% of me here
and 50% of me there. You know what I mean?
Where. like. I'm probably more split.
It's not gonna be as easy for me
to jump into something here.
I didn't wanna give you 50
and have you give me a hundred.
Obviously. Carmen has feelings
for this other guy.
That sucks.
I think she wouldn't be
spending this time with me and getting...
I don't think she'd be doing this
if she didn't like me.
I don't know.
It's just so hard to get in her head.
She's keeping her cards so close.
-I have a proposition.
-Okay.
So. you're 50 in. 50 out.
How about you be 100% in here...
and then decide
what you wanna do at the end?
I feel like I can give you...
80.
Ah... Okay. I'll take it.
But I do still feel like. at least
for now especially. maybe I'll get to 100.
but I feel like while I'm at 80.
we are gonna sleep outside.
But that's the one part
where I'm gonna have to be...
Sleeping outside. I get that.
I get it's a respect thing. and I'm just
putting that out there. I don't want to.
[narrator] Looks like Bergie
is chatting to Allie again.
You know what? This could be the
"Bergie-ning" of a beautiful relationship.
I am so sorry.
How is. uh. how is your day going?
Good.
And how are you feeling
about people in the villa?
-I've been fighting for a lot of girls.
-Yeah.
And everybody knows that I'm interested...
Yeah. Yeah.
[both laugh]
...in them. so. I'm just like.
"All right. now it's their time
to show that they're interested back."
Yeah. right.
And I don't want you to think I'm not.
but the last thing I want is for you
to feel led on or hurt ever again.
-It sucks.
-Like. no. truly.
I'm just being completely upfront.
I'm not entirely sure.
I feel like Bergie and I
have a connection.
Um. I'm just not entirely sure
if he can give me what I need.
and if that's something
that will come with time.
or if that's just two different
personalities that just don't mesh.
I'm not trying
to win a ticket to stay here longer.
If I'm not a hundred percent in anything.
I will not continue.
-Gotcha.
-Because it's just not worth it to me.
-I'm not entirely sure what this is.
-No. Which way you wanna go.
I'm not entirely...
I don't know anything. [laughing]
Like. I don't know shit.
And I'm not gonna pretend to.
Yeah. I just wanted to pull you
to let you know I'm still interested
to getting to know you.
-Yeah. For sure.
-I just want to let you know.
-you're in my top area.
-[both laughing]
"My top area."
-How are you? [giggles]
-Good.
-How are you?
So. I know today. you know.
might have been a lot for you.
I mean. yeah. It was definitely
kind of crazy coming in.
like. you know. for you.
Um. you know...
I don't know. 'cause I've never...
This sounds so conceited.
but I mean. I've never...
been kind of rejected before.
Don't look at it as rejection.
That's stupid. It's not rejection.
I mean. that is rejection. isn't it?
Yeah. but I'm being...
I'm not... I'm being respectful.
I think it's like...
You know. people grow apart.
people grow in different paths.
Mm-hmm. It just felt kind of blindsided
'cause I thought it would have
meant a little bit more to you.
But I just feel that maybe
you weren't being honest then... back then.
Do you think you were?
Definitely not saying anything at all
is not the best way to go about things...
-Mm-hmm.
-...and I admit that. I'm sorry for that.
Maybe if I would have said
I did like you. it could have been better.
I stood in that mirror.
and I was there thinking.
"Okay. you know what? I needed more."
I needed more from you. And I guess
you weren't willing to give me more. so...
You didn't text me
over the days when I texted you.
It was real small. short messages back.
All you sent me were pictures.
Hey. I'm not good at... I wasn't good
at verbalizing my feelings and stuff.
[laughs]
Nothing wrong with that. I have some room
to work on it. but I'm getting better.
Yeah. I guess... I don't know. I just...
I don't think I really appreciated...
I'm not saying that you led me on.
but I just felt like
for that long period of time.
you knew. obviously.
I had feelings for you.
And. like. I don't think
it was reciprocated.
Like. I feel like
you could've told me that before.
You know. I'm sorry for that.
And I know you seeing me
being able to open up to a girl...
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-...is hard to watch. I'm sure.
Especially when you're like.
"Why couldn't he do this with me?"
Clearing the air with Marco
was definitely the closure that I needed.
Sometimes. you know.
the hard truth is what you need to hear.
But I feel like. "Okay. whew!
Weight lifted off our shoulder."
I know that is done and over with.
and I'm just happy
to be friends with him at this point.
Well. thank you for apologizing.
um. and I'm happy that you're happy.
I appreciate it.
And your happiness could be around here.
-We'll see.
-You're in Fiji.
Yeah.
Where else would you wanna be?
I know.
Tell me something
about you that I don't know.
Do you play an instrument?
I used to play the piano.
-Really?
-For a couple years. yeah.
-It was when I was younger.
-Can you sing?
But I was actually pretty good at it.
I don't know why I stopped.
I play a little bit of the guitar.
-Really? Did you teach yourself?
-Yeah.
Uh. my grandfather also plays.
Are you close with your grandpa?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Where does he live?
-He lives closer to Sacramento.
Okay. so California.
Is all of your family in California?
No. I have family in Louisiana.
I have family in Florida. Alabama.
-Do you have a big ass fam...
-I don't know how...
I'm gonna cover a lot of states. I'm not
gonna do this. We'll be here all night.
Yeah. Wait. how big is your family?
So on my dad's side.
we have a lot of longevity in our lines.
-Okay.
-So. like. I have a...
There's a paper...
a newspaper clip somewhere.
Having four generations alive
at one period of time is very rare.
Yeah. That's like me
with my mom's side too.
Shit.
Goddamn.
Are we related?
-Fuck. I hope not.
-I'm just kidding.
-My God. Jonah.
I'm not from Alabama.
How you feeling
about all the other guys here?
I mean. everyone's super cool. super nice.
But there's no one else that really
I've been super. super excited to talk to
or get to know other than you.
Well. shit.
Not to pump your ego or anything.
[scoffs] Like my head needs
to get any fucking bigger.
Mm-hmm. How about
your chats with the other girls?
It's been good. but definitely.
so far. the easiest person to chat with
and get along with has been you.
-Aw. stop.
-Yeah.
There could definitely be
a potential romantic spark with Taylor C.
We have great conversations
that they don't need
to go in depth for us to get each other.
And I think that's what
I've kind of been missing here.
You don't necessarily need the deep
questions to have a deeper connection.
Sometimes it's just relating.
sometimes it's friendly banter.
sometimes it's just getting along
and having a genuine conversation.
So that's something
that I'm gonna continue to pursue.
So. are you gonna be back
in my bed again tonight?
Yeah. I'll be in your bed tonight.
♪ Just stay by my side ♪
♪ I think you know
You got me stuck on you all night ♪
♪ And I don't want you
To leave me this time ♪
♪ Oh. baby boy. I can see it ♪
♪ I see in your eyes ♪
♪ Lost in this place with you ♪
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Destiny and Zay only have conversations
that feature no artificial ingredients
or use of pesticides.
After we had that first conversation.
it was very organic.
I feel like that's very rare
to come by honestly.
[giggles] Really?
Yeah. Did you have fun at the game?
I loved the game.
Pure bliss. Okay?
Well. I'm glad it was with us.
Did you enjoy it?
-I loved it. I had a great time.
-You loved it? Yeah.
And even. like... It's just a game.
When I was making out with Kassy. you're
not even thinking about kissing her.
-Yeah. you're not.
-You're thinking about...
-Winning.
-...accomplishing what you have to do.
Like. me and her. our teeth were
banging off each other. It was just like...
No. that's what I said about our kiss.
They were like. "That was aggressive."
Like. I just didn't waste any... [laughing]
Yeah. It was just like...
...I wasted no time.
I can do this. you know.
when we're actually meaning it. like...
Sensual. more sensual.
More sensual. you know?
Let me throw passion in. 'Cause at first.
I'm just like. "Let's go!"
-Yes.
-"Let's go!"
-I would have kept going. you know?
-I would've too.
Yeah. We can keep doing it.
We can keep doing it.
[laughs]
Okay!
People can say
whatever they want about Destiny.
but they cannot say she does not
get the best-looking man. Okay?
That was like.
"Okay. this could go somewhere."
[singsongy] I am so excited.
Aw. you're making me smile.
Good. you should smile more.
I like that. Give me a hug. pooh-pooh.
Oh. Des.
[Destiny] Give me a hug.
Baby.
After being friend-zoned by Allie.
Bergie's decided
to have a chat with Taylor S.
I've actually never been up here.
Yeah. you have to lay down.
It's like the most romantic spot
in the villa.
-It is? Well. cheers to that.
-Cheers to that.
What is... What do you like to do on. like.
I guess. like.
a weekend with your friends?
-We just go out. barhop.
-Barhop. Yeah.
I'm a homebody too.
I love just cooking.
Making brownies on a Friday night.
eating the whole tray.
-Do you love cooking?
-I love cooking so much.
What is your favorite thing to make?
'Cause I'm a big cook too.
I love cooking as well.
So. before I left. I made a chocolate
Swiss cake roll for the first time.
-I baked it.
-Oh. fuck.
That was amazing.
-Oh. my God.
-Yeah.
That sounds so good.
I have it written in my journal
on how to make it too.
I heard that you make good...
-Chocolate chip pancakes?
-...pancakes. Yes.
I can make some tomorrow.
So one of my love languages
is doing acts of service.
Mine is as well. I'm very
words of affirmation and acts of service.
I love that.
You've really surprised me.
I mean. I feel very comfortable.
You feel like a safe space.
Thank you.
And I am attracted to you. so...
I'm attracted to you as well.
So. my door closed with Allie.
I felt it was closed.
and I wasn't gonna keep pursuing
and trying to reopen that door.
I'm still optimistic. and I'm just
ready to explore other options
and see what everybody else has to offer.
How was your chats with everyone else?
Really good. but I really enjoyed ours.
So I was wondering. would you like
to sleep in my bed tonight?
Sure. Why not? Yeah.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Yeah. yeah. yeah.
[both laughing]
No. you don't say "thank you." Bergie.
I know. That's why I said it twice.
I was like.
"Why did I just say thank you?"
But I'm gonna say
thank you again. Oh. my gosh.
Yes. I will sleep in your bed tonight.
Let's go.
[narrator] I don't know if Dasja
thinks she's at a karaoke bar.
'cause she's about to take the Mike.
I know you and I.
you know. we've talked a lot.
You haven't pulled anybody else
for a chat. have you?
No. I haven't.
I've been a little preoccupied.
Have my hands full with you.
Oh. I love that.
Yeah.
I love that.
You get a little vibe in here?
Nice little vibes between you and I.
So. question for you.
Okay. hit me.
Um. I know you were getting to know. um.
was it just Destiny in the villa?
I'd say right now. it's just really...
Destiny is the only one
that I've been seriously getting to know.
She just was the only one that I felt
like an initial. you know. connection.
I feel like I get a similar vibe from you...
-Yeah.
-...just initially. you know?
Obviously. we got a lot to...
you know. we got a lot of ground to cover.
We do. Yeah. we do.
But I feel like
we're off to a good start so far.
I agree.
Yeah.
Don't be looking at me like that.
Looking at you like what?
You know.
I don't know.
I'll let you figure it out.
Right now.
you're definitely catching my eye.
Yeah. That's safe to say.
You're making me blush.
Man.
I have had a bit more time
with Destiny. so maybe this isn't fair.
But I don't wanna close off completely
and kind of build walls before I chat
to another single girl in the villa.
And right now... [clicks tongue] ...Dasja.
she's a solid contender
for the girl who's gonna end up. you know.
with a. uh...
with a piece of this heart. so...
You have good eye contact too.
-For real?
-Yeah. You know?
Thank you.
Do I?
But there's
one last test to see if we click.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And that is?
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
The Casa boys
are getting down to business.
and Kyle's with Imani.
How are we feeling?
I feel good.
And I'm just on cloud nine right now.
-Honestly?
-Yeah.
-You make me feel really good.
-Aw.
Very appreciated.
and just valued. and just...
You definitely aim to get to know me.
and the way you just go in
and break down the walls. like...
I'm like. "Let me in." I'm knocking.
"Let me in. Open up that doggone door."
Oh. my God. you're so silly.
You know that? Yeah.
That's how I know I like you.
'cause I feel like I can be me.
-Yeah.
-And I can be stupid as hell.
And you just here cracking up with me.
I love that about us. for real.
Me too. I feel like
we definitely have something great here.
Mmm. I just like our vibe a lot.
We do have an amazing vibe.
And I can look at your eyes
all goddamn day.
-Thank you.
-And I ain't even lying.
You're so sweet. [giggles]
[Imani] I really like him.
Like. I genuinely
really. really. really like him.
It's just getting better
and better and better. like...
[chuckles]
[squeals]
Imani. I really like you.
-You like me? How much?
-I do. I really do.
-How much?
-Yeah.
That much.
That's a lot of like.
[both laughing]
I wanna go inside.
It's kind of loud out here.
-Wanna go in the bedroom?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Oh. God. Now Kassy and Matia
are going to the bedroom.
Aw. shit. Who knows
what's gonna happen in there?
Fuck. [sniggers]
She keeps trying to. like. be like...
[Hannah W] Mmm.
"Leo. ra-ra-ra"...
The thing is. it's like...
Leo compared to him...
There ain't no comparison in my opinion.
I know who I would pick.
-Who would you pick?
-Him.
I don't like him.
All my conversations
with him are just very shallow.
She's kind of shallow.
[laughing] She kind of is. She's always
talking about herself and shit.
-You think maybe it balances?
-She's very unaware.
If he's very shallow. all about himself.
and she's very unaware of everything.
-I think it's a match made in heaven.
-I just love Leo.
I almost feel like Leo's too good for her.
Anyways. how are you doing?
I'm good. I feel good.
But at the same time...
It looks so good on you.
Yeah?
I've made it pretty clear.
my intentions. like.
I'm not here to fuck around
and waste someone's time.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
I'm kind of at a point in my life
where I want something more serious.
Mmm. Yeah.
So...
No. same.
Coming in here. like.
I wasn't expecting anything.
And I hope you know
the reason why I'm not going full in
is because I have something...
someone else in the villa.
No. then... I get that.
Since meeting you. I was like.
"Okay. there's something there
that I don't think I can deny."
"I can't brush off."
I wish we have more time.
It takes me time to open up to people.
-Yeah.
-Like. I'm a little more reserved.
-Um...
But yeah. with time.
I get. like... I'm pretty funny.
-Okay. Well. I can see that.
-I'm pretty fucking random.
I can see funny stuff is...
-But I also like how mature you are.
-Yeah.
Like. even when I'm around you.
I get. like. shy or quiet.
Well. I'm shy.
-Yeah.
So. I'm just. um. in a pickle.
-At least now I've laid my cards out.
-Mmm.
You see both decks. Now you choose.
-Yeah.
-Can I give you a kiss on the cheek?
-Aw. thank you.
-Okay. let's go.
I don't know.
What do you think about Kay Kay?
Look at her smiling over there.
[laughing]
Yay!
-She ain't gonna leave Keenan.
-No.
Sometimes I just wanna slap her.
You don't know what Keenan
is doing right now.
His head sways with the wind.
I just want to hope
that he's actually taking Casa to be like.
"This is my opportunity
to prove myself to Kay Kay
because I've let her down in the past."
You don't think he's doing that?
Not at all.
I feel like he's just angry at Kay Kay.
Like. she's not the problem.
but she's getting treated like it.
I feel like he's been hurt by past trauma.
Other women?
Women.
And she gets the brunt of it.
But that's something
you need to work out within yourself.
Not on this beautiful girl.
And I've dated men like that
who just aren't happy with themselves.
Yeah.
And it's like. I want you to know that.
like. I don't want you to feel pressured
in any way. It's been like...
I wanna make sure you know
it's just. fun. flirty. enjoyable.
Even tonight. I might even sleep outside.
I'm not telling you where I'm sleeping.
Okay. first of all. let me just tell you.
-sleeping outside is amazing.
-Really?
I woke up to the most beautiful view.
Sunrise?
Yeah. And the sun woke me up. you know?
-Mm-hmm.
-It was actually nice.
I don't know what's gonna happen.
I think I might just be trying to put
all my eggs in the Kay Kay basket now.
And I hope it doesn't
topple over and crack everywhere.
But that's the place I've seen
the most connection and growth really.
I don't think there's any way
we can force her to bring someone back.
-because if it was up to us...
-Definitely not.
...we would be like. "Go for Brandon."
But I'm not gonna
shove it down her throat.
No. I'm done with it.
So I feel like all we can do
is support the decision she's making.
-And if she gets hurt. be there.
-And we can't support it. but be there.
Yeah. for sure.
As I'm here. I'm trying my best
not to think about Keenan.
Yeah. as you should.
-And I'm doing a good job.
-Yeah. I think you have.
Honestly. I'm just having fun.
I'm doing me.
But you know
that I have deep feelings for Keenan.
I know.
And I would hate
to play with anybody's emotions.
Yeah.
How are you feeling?
I feel like you got some questions for me.
I do.
Let's have some talks. then.
So. you know how earlier. you were like.
you wanna make sure that we connect on a...
on a "sexual" connection?
I already know we connect there. 100%.
-I know. but I'm saying I wanna do. like...
-More?
...more time of just really getting to know
each other. being in depth.
and. you know.
seeing how much that can grow.
'Cause I really am interested.
♪ I tried to tell a story... ♪
Oh. my God.
-Extra?
-Yeah.
Girl. get the fuck off me.
'cause... [stammers]
-Come here. Come here.
-No.
-No. 'cause I almost messed up.
-I'm about to knock this pillow...
'Cause I almost messed up.
I literally just almost messed up.
-It's okay.
-No.
Ooh. you're... Stop.
Shit.
Don't say no.
Come here.
Exactly. I need a minute.
I'm horny as fuck. I gotta walk away.
[both giggling]
Just deep breathe. You can't even see.
Yeah. 'cause it's in my waistline.
Come here. honey.
You are really a dangerous creature.
♪ Do we step into the light?
Let the sunlight burn us ♪
♪ Peel off the skin
That's kept the truth inside us ♪
Do not do that to me. I'm hard as...
Stop. you cannot touch me.
You cannot touch me right now.
Like. stop.
Goddamn.
Come on. you admitting
you just want to feel that?
I'm about to hit you
with this damn pillow.
You need to cover up right now.
Okay. I'm gonna leave you alone.
Your body is terrific.
And your face is terrific.
And you look pretty without makeup on.
-[phone chimes]
-I got a text.
[all] Oh. shit.
It's a video.
[gasps] Stop!
A special delivery...
Oh. fuck.
...causes chaos.
[sobbing] This is so fucked up.
[sobbing]
[theme song playing]